Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 2: Boxes 23-43
Archives Information File, Section 2: Boxes 23-43
- Box: 28, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Item 6: Reports of Foreman Conferences, 1924; Publication (Box 28, Folder 25)
    Author: Forman Conference Group
  - Item 7: Report of Conference on Improving Foremanship, 1925; Publication (Box 28, Folder 25)
    Author: Conference on Improving Foremanship
    Notes: November 10 - March 23, 1924-1925
- Box: 28, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Foreman Training Essential to Plant Self-Government, 1926; Publication (Box 28, Folder 26)
    Author: Cyrus McCormick
    Notes: June 1926
- Box: 28, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Trends in Foremen Thinking, 1948; Publication (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Progress Report on Foremen Thinking, 1952; Publication (Box 28, Folder 27)
    Notes: December 1952
  - Item 3: Recent Trends in Foremen Thinking, 1950; Publication (Box 28, Folder 27)
    Notes: November 1950
  - Item 4: Foremen Morale Strong as Companies Gear for Stiffer Competition, 1954; Publication (Box 28, Folder 27)
    Notes: May 1954
  - Item 5: Latest Trends on Foremen Thinking and the Productivity Problem, 1957; Publication (Box 28, Folder 27)
    Notes: February 1957
  - Item 6: Developing Foremen into Real Managers, 1960; Publication (Box 28, Folder 27)
    Notes: February 1960
  - Item 7: What Motivates the Foreman in Raising Productivity, 1958; Publication (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Item 8: Foremen Morale Strong as Companies Gear for Stiffer Competition, 1954; Publication (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Item 9: Supervision Management's Vital Link, 1957; Publication (Box 28, Folder 27)
    Author: Institute of Industrial Supervisors
  - Item 10: How You Can Teach Workers to Solve Problems on the Job, 1949; Publication (Box 28, Folder 27)
    Author: National Foremen's Institute
  - Item 11: The Status of the Foreman, 1948; Publication (Box 28, Folder 27)
    Author: Birmingham Central Technical College
    Notes: November 1948
  - Item 12: The Foreman and His Problems, 1947; Publication (Box 28, Folder 27)
    Author: G.H. Alexander
  - Item 13: Getting Effective Leadership in the Industrial Organization, Publication (Box 28, Folder 27)
    Author: Douglas McGregor
  - Item 14: The Foreman and Productivity, Publication (Box 28, Folder 27)
    Author: Percy H. Mills
  - Item 15: A Report on Foremanship Attitudes, 1946; Publication (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Item 16: The Supervisor's Concern with Costs in an Electric Power Company, 1953; Publication (Box 28, Folder 27)
    Author: Floyd Mann & Howard Baumgartel
    Notes: July 1953
  - Item 17: Automotive Company Practices with Respect to Foremen, Publication (Box 28, Folder 27)
    Author: Automotive Council for War Production
  - Item 18: The Foreman on His Job, 1941; Publication (Box 28, Folder 27)
    Author: A.L. Kress
    Notes: October 1941
  - Item 19: Foremanship Fundamentals, 1941; Publication (Box 28, Folder 27)
    Notes: June 1941
- Box: 28, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Management of Personnel Quarterly, 1965; Publication (Box 28, Folder 28)
    Notes: Summer 1965
  - Item 2: The Case of the Immature Assistant, Publication (Box 28, Folder 28)
    Author: Dartnell Corporations
  - Item 3: Analisis de Necesidades de los Mandos Intermedios, 1969; Publication (Box 28, Folder 28)
    Author: Instituto Technologico y de Estudios Superiores de Monterrey
- Box: 28, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Management of Personnel Quarterly, 1962; Publication (Box 28, Folder 29)
    Notes: Autumn-Winter 1962
  - Item 2: Morale Index for Supervisors, 1962; Publication (Box 28, Folder 29)
    Author: Leadership Resources, Inc.
  - Item 3: Master ma Proizuodstue, 1968; Publication (Box 28, Folder 29)
    Author: N.F. Zaruhou
- Box: 28, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Status of First-Level Supervisors, 1971; Publication (Box 28, Folder 30)
    Notes: November 1971
  - Item 2: Om Arbetsledare en Bibliografi, 1969; Publication (Box 28, Folder 30)
    Author: Svenska Arbetsgivareforeningen
- Box: 28, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: The Importance of Foreman, Publication (Box 28, Folder 31)
    Author: Tsuneo Ohuchi
- Box: 28, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Supervisor Development Program: Position & Pay Management, 1962; Publication (Box 28, Folder 32)
    Author: U.S. Department of the Army
- Box: 28, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Foreman's Handbook, 1937; Publication (Box 28, Folder 33)
    Author: Works Progress Administration
    Notes: November 1937
  - Item 2: Manuals for Executives and Supervisors, 1941; Publication (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Item 3: Preparation and Use of Organization and Procedure Manuals: Selected Readings, 1949; Publication (Box 28, Folder 33)
    Notes: October 1949
- Box: 28, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Statement of Robert H. Keys, 1947; Publication (Box 28, Folder 34)
    Author: Robert H. Keys
    Notes: February 19, 1947
  - Item 2: The Right of Foremen to Organize for the Purpose of Collective Bargaining in Sweden, 1943; Publication (Box 28, Folder 34)
    Author: James J. Robbins
    Notes: June 1, 1943
  - Item 3: A History of the Movement to Organize Foremen in the Automobile Industry, Publication (Box 28, Folder 34)
    Author: General Motor Corporation
  - Item 4: The Organization of Foremen and Supervisors, Publication (Box 28, Folder 34)
    Author: John Truesdale
  - Item 5: An Analysis of Foreman-Steward Power Relationships, 1949; Publication (Box 28, Folder 34)
    Author: Eugene Jacobson
- Box: 28, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Foremen's Salary Survey; Metal Industry, 1949; Publication (Box 28, Folder 35)
    Author: The Employers' Association of Chicago
    Notes: May 1949
  - Item 2: Automotive Company Practices with Respect to Foremen, Publication (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Item 3: Automotive Company Practices with Respect to Foremen, Publication (Box 28, Folder 35)
- Box: 28, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Appraising Key Man Performance, 1963; Publication (Box 28, Folder 36)
    Author: Eugene J. Benge
  - Item 2: Managerial Appraisal Programs, 1964; Publication (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Item 3: Selecting and Training Potential Foremen and Supervisors, 1967; Publication (Box 28, Folder 36)
    Author: Donald L. Kirkpatrick
  - Item 4: Essential Facts on the British Foreman, 1965; Publication (Box 28, Folder 36)
    Author: Anthony Hamblin, Keith Thurley & Dolores Voon
  - Item 5: How Do You Rate?, Publication (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Item 6: Selecting Supervisors for the Public Service, Publication (Box 28, Folder 36)
    Author: John M. Pfiffner, Joseph W. Hawthorne, Harold Fields
  - Item 7: Measuring Supervisory Ability- A Case Study, 1950; Publication (Box 28, Folder 36)
    Author: Industrial Relations Counselors
    Notes: September 22, 1950
- Box: 28, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Technological Changes in Plywood Occupations, 1968; Publication (Box 28, Folder 37)
    Author: U.S. Employment Service
- Box: 28, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: The Forest Wealth of the Soviet Far East and its Exploitation, 1936; Publication (Box 28, Folder 38)
    Author: A. Tsymek
- Box: 29, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Forest Labour Force in Finland, 1965; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Author: Lauri Heikinheimo, Toini Ristimaki
- Box: 29, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: A Philosophy for a Foundation, 1963; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Author: Raymond B. Fosdick
  - Item 2: Before the Special Committee to Investigate Tax Exempt Foundations, Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Author: Rockeller Foundation
- Box: 29, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Selected Information on Foundations and Their Grants, 1961; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Box: 29, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Preneed Burial Service, 1964; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Author: U.S. Special Committee on Aging
    Notes: May 19, 1964
- Box: 29, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Organizing Society for Freedom, 1964; Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: The Spiritual and Moral Significance of Free Enterprise, 1961; Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Notes: December 6, 1961
  - Item 3: Speak Up Management, 1944; Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Seeds of Growth, 1965; Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Author: Roger M. Blough
  - Item 5: How Free is Free Enterprise?, Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Author: George Meany
  - Item 6: Economic Attitudes in Industry, 1932; Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Author: F.C. Caldwell, C.A. Norman, John Younger
    Notes: January 1932
  - Item 7: Economic Liberalism and Free Enterprise, 1944; Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Author: Benjamin L. Masse
  - Item 8: Free Enterprise the American Way, 1946; Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Author: M.E. Coyle
    Notes: December 3, 1946
  - Item 9: The American Competitive Enterprise System, 1946; Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Are Federal Corporations a Threat to Free Enterprise?, Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Author: American Economic Foundation
  - Item 11: The Free Enterprise System, 1948; Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Author: Phelps Adams
    Notes: January 5, 1948
  - Item 12: Constructive Industrial Practices, 1939; Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Notes: June 1939
  - Item 13: Employee Understanding of a Free Market Economy, Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Author: L.C. Michelon
  - Item 14: Free Enterprise in America, 1962; Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Box: 29, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The American Worker's Stake in Foreign Trade, 1962; Publication (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: A New Trade Policy for the United States, 1962; Publication (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Notes: April 1962
- Box: 29, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Worker's Right to Unite, Publication (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Author: W. Hug
- Box: 29, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Rapport sur la Situation Energetique de la Communaute et Perspectives d'approvisionnement et de Consommation d'energie dans la Communaute in 1962, Publication (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Author: European Coal and Steel Community
- Box: 29, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: A Plan for the Restoration of Employment, 1933; Publication (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Author: Edward Bennett
    Notes: January 20, 1933
  - Item 2: A Practical Program for the Prevention of Unemployment in America, 1914; Publication (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Author: John B. Andrews
    Notes: December 1914
  - Item 3: Full Employment in Practice, 1946; Publication (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Author: John H.G. Pierson
  - Item 4: The Public and a Program for Industrial Harmony, 1939; Publication (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Author: A.W. Hawkes
    Notes: December 8, 1939
- Box: 29, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Fur Industry, 1946; Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
    Author: Russel R. Taylor
- Box: 29, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Health Hazards in the Fur Industry, 1942; Publication (Box 29, Folder 11)
    Author: Harry Hiemann
    Notes: December 1942
- Box: 29, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Trends in the Furniture Manufacturing Industry, 1944; Publication (Box 29, Folder 12)
    Author: George L. Leffler, Mary Virginia Brown
- Box: 29, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Industry Wage Studies: Furniture, 1947; Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
    Notes: February 1947
- Box: 29, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Occupational Information on Furniture Manufacturing in North Carolina, 1947; Publication (Box 29, Folder 14)
    Author: North Carolina Employment Security Commission
- Box: 29, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Wage Structure: Metal Furniture, 1947; Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
    Notes: October 1947
- Box: 29, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Furniture Manufacture, 1967; Publication (Box 29, Folder 16)
    Author: Great Britain Central Youth Employment Executive
- Box: 29, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Game Theory and Human Conflicts, 1966; Publication (Box 29, Folder 17)
    Author: Klaus-Peter Heiss
- Box: 29, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Federal Wage-Garnishment Law, 1970; Publication (Box 29, Folder 18)
    Notes: October 1970
  - Item 2: Wage Exemptions and Time of Action for Garnishment: The Law in Wisconsin and Other States, 1964; Publication (Box 29, Folder 18)
    Author: Legislative Reference Bureau
- Box: 29, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Die Lohnpfandung, Publication (Box 29, Folder 19)
    Author: Erich Feil
- Box: 29, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Report of the Committee on Development and Use of Gas Industry Statistics, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    Author: Robert E. Ginna
  - Item 2: La Greve Generale en Belgique, 1961; Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
    Author: Centre de Recherche et D'Information Socio-Politiques
- Box: 29, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: French General Strike, 1968; Publication (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Box: 29, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: A Souvenir of the General Strike, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    Author: The British Gazette
- Box: 29, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: The Bonn Constitution, 1949; Publication (Box 29, Folder 23)
    Notes: June 1949
  - Item 2: Der Tag der Volkserhelung, Publication (Box 29, Folder 23)
    Author: Der Bundesvorstand des Deutschen Gewerkschaftsbundes
    Notes: June 17
- Box: 29, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: The Beginnings and Development of German Business History, 1952; Publication (Box 29, Folder 24)
    Author: Fritz Redlich
    Notes: September 1952
- Box: 29, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Die Vierte Novelle zum Gesetz zu Artikel 131 GG, 1966; Publication (Box 29, Folder 25)
    Author: Georg Anders
  - Item 2: The Way to the Completion of the Socialist Construction of the German Democratic Republic, 1964; Publication (Box 29, Folder 25)
    Author: The Council of State of the German Democratic Republic
- Box: 29, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Report of the Commission Appointed to Enquire into Salaries and Wages of the Civil Service and Non-Government Teaching Service, 1957, Publication (Box 29, Folder 26)
    Author: Government of Ghana
  - Item 2: Government Proposals on the Report of the Salaries and Wages Commission, 1957, Publication (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Report of the Ghana Administrative Committee on Matters Connected with the Revision of Salaries and Wages, 1957, Publication (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Box: 29, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Glassmaking at Jamestown, 1952; Publication (Box 29, Folder 27)
    Author: J.C. Harrington
- Box: 29, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: The Role of Gold, 1963; Publication (Box 29, Folder 28)
    Author: Arthur Kemp
- Box: 29, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: An Italian Experiment: State Industry Competes with Private Enterprise, Publication (Box 29, Folder 29)
    Author: Istituto per la Ricostruzionne Industriale
- Box: 29, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Salary and Wage Practices of State Highway Departments, 1947; Publication (Box 29, Folder 30)
    Author: National Research Council
    Notes: December 1947
- Box: 29, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Salary and Wage Administration in the Public Service, 1946; Publication (Box 29, Folder 31)
    Notes: December 1946
- Box: 29, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Nationalised Industries in Britain, 1964; Publication (Box 29, Folder 32)
    Author: British Information Services
  - Item 2: Efficiency in the Nationalised Industries, 1952; Publication (Box 29, Folder 32)
    Author: Institute of Public Administration
  - Item 3: Problems of Public Ownership, 1952; Publication (Box 29, Folder 32)
    Author: Ernest Davies
  - Item 4: Workers' Control?, 1949; Publication (Box 29, Folder 32)
    Author: Eirene White
  - Item 5: British Industrial Relations and Nationalization, Publication (Box 29, Folder 32)
    Author: Bertram F. Collins
  - Item 6: Workers' Control, 1951; Publication (Box 29, Folder 32)
    Notes: January 1951
  - Item 7: What is a Socialised Industry?, Publication (Box 29, Folder 32)
    Author: Michael Young
  - Item 8: Consumers' Councils, 1953; Publication (Box 29, Folder 32)
    Author: Mary Stewart
    Notes: January 1, 1953
- Box: 29, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Small Business and Government Procurement, 1962; Publication (Box 29, Folder 33)
    Notes: December 17, 1962
- Box: 29, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Government Small Business Procurement Practices and Programs, 1964; Publication (Box 29, Folder 34)
    Notes: December 24, 1964
  - Item 2: Economic Impact of Federal Supply and Service Activities, 1964; Publication (Box 29, Folder 34)
- Box: 29, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Government Expenditures, 1966; Publication (Box 29, Folder 35)
    Author: Association of American Railroads
  - Item 2: Government Expenditures for Transport Facilities, 1967; Publication (Box 29, Folder 35)
    Notes: March 1967
- Box: 29, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Maximum Grant Rates, 1965; Publication (Box 29, Folder 36)
    Notes: December 1965
- Box: 29, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Government Reorganization and Revenue-Sharing, Publication (Box 29, Folder 37)
- Box: 29, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Labour's Colonial Policy, Publication (Box 29, Folder 38)
- Box: 29, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Distribution of Industry, 1948; Publication (Box 29, Folder 39)
    Author: His Majesty's Stationery Office
    Notes: October 1948
  - Item 2: Britain and the Common Market, Publication (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Item 3: The Industrial Charter, 1947; Publication (Box 29, Folder 39)
    Author: Conservative and Unionist Central Office
    Notes: May 1947
  - Item 4: Proud Heritage, 1949; Publication (Box 29, Folder 39)
- Box: 29, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Working for Prosperity, 1965; Publication (Box 29, Folder 40)
    Author: Great Britain Department of Economic Affairs and the Central Office of Information
  - Item 2: The Task Ahead: Economic Assessment, 1969; Publication (Box 29, Folder 40)
    Author: Great Britain Department of Economic Affairs
  - Item 3: The British Economy, 1966; Publication (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Item 4: 50 Facts About Britain's Economy, 1967; Publication (Box 29, Folder 40)
- Box: 29, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: The Wage Packet: How the Economy Works, 1967; Publication (Box 29, Folder 41)
    Author: Philip Hanson
  - Item 2: Economic Trends, 1954; Publication (Box 29, Folder 41)
    Author: Great Britain Central Statistical Office
- Box: 29, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: The British Economic Problem, 1968; Publication (Box 29, Folder 42)
    Author: Hill, Samuel & Co.
  - Item 2: Guidelines for Growth and for Incomes in the United Kingdom: Some Possible Lessons for the United States, 1966; Publication (Box 29, Folder 42)
    Author: E.H. Phelps Brown
- Box: 29, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Report of the British Section on Migration of Workers, 1930; Publication (Box 29, Folder 43)
    Author: International Association for Social Progress
- Box: 29, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Industrial Britain, 1954; Publication (Box 29, Folder 44)
    Author: Duncan Crow
  - Item 2: What's Wrong with British Industry?, 1964; Publication (Box 29, Folder 44)
    Author: Rex Malik
  - Item 3: The Structure and Efficiency of British Industry, 1970; Publication (Box 29, Folder 44)
    Author: Research Publications Services
    Notes: July 1970
- Box: 29, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: The Industrial Revolution in England, 1966; Publication (Box 29, Folder 45)
    Author: R.M. Hartwell
  - Item 2: In Pudding-Time: The Early Stages of Industrialization, 1962; Publication (Box 29, Folder 45)
    Author: D.E.C. Eversley
- Box: 29, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: National Health Service: The Future Structure of the National Health Service, 1970; Publication (Box 29, Folder 46)
    Author: Great Britain Department of Health and Social Security
  - Item 2: National Health Service Superannuation Scheme, 1962; Publication (Box 29, Folder 46)
    Author: Great Britain Ministry of Health
- Box: 29, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: The Civil Service General, Scientific and Technical Posts, 1964; Publication (Box 29, Folder 47)
    Author: Great Britain Ministry of Labour
- Box: 29, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Wage Policies in the Public Sector, 1962; Publication (Box 29, Folder 48)
    Notes: November 19, 1962
- Box: 29, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: That was the Promise that was Tory Words and Tory Deeds, Publication (Box 29, Folder 49)
    Author: Labour Research Department
- Box: 29, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Key Statistics of the British Economy, Publication (Box 29, Folder 50)
    Author: London & Cambridge Economic Service
- Box: 29, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: The Industrial Society's Guide to the Report of the Royal Commission on Trade Unions and Employers' Associations, 1969; Publication (Box 29, Folder 51)
    Notes: July 1969
- Box: 29, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: The Local Democrat, Publication (Box 29, Folder 52)
    Author: George Dickson
- Box: 29, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 29, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: International Labor Migration, 1966; Publication (Box 29, Folder 53)
    Author: Xenophon Zolotas
- Box: 30, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A Tribute to William Green, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Author: Jewish Labor Committee
- Box: 30, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: How to Handle Grievances, 1943; Publication (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Author: Glenn Gardiner
  - Item 2: Grievance Procedures and Joint Labor Relations Committees, Publication (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Author: New York Department of Health
  - Item 3: Human Problems in Production Supervision, 1941; Publication (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Author: Joseph H. Vertrees
  - Item 4: Handling Grievances, 1944; Publication (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Author: Philadelphia Chamber of Commerce and Board of Trade
    Notes: February 1944
  - Item 5: 114 Check Points on how to Prevent Grievances, 1953; Publication (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Author: Bleick von Bleicken and Carl Heyel
    Notes: January 1953
  - Item 6: Grievance Procedures, 1947; Publication (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Author: The Montreal Board of Trade
    Notes: March 20, 1947
- Box: 30, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Evaluation and Implementation Machinery, 1961; Publication (Box 30, Folder 3)
    Author: India Ministry of Labour and Employment